What if I told you that not all species fit neatly into r or K categories?
In ecology, r and K selection describe life strategies.
R strategists reproduce quickly, while K strategists invest in fewer offspring.
But there's more!
Not all species strictly adhere to these labels.
Some blend traits from both strategies.
Consider species like turtles and elephants; they show characteristics of both r and K selection, defying the simple definitions.
Understanding these nuances helps us grasp the complexity of life.
It’s not black and white; nature is a spectrum.
Curious about more biology insights?
Hit that follow for more science mysteries!