Uranium dating reveals ages that carbon can't even touch.
Geochronology is all about timing—literally.
While carbon dating stops at about 50,000 years, uranium-lead dating goes back billions.
Imagine rocks that formed when dinosaurs roamed...or even before!
This method unlocks Earth’s deepest history.
Uranium decays slowly over time, providing a reliable clock.
Scientists use it to date zircon crystals—some over 4 billion years old!
So next time you think of ancient time, remember: uranium-lead dating is the key to Earth's age-old secrets.
Want to dive deeper into geology?
Hit like, subscribe, and explore the mysteries of our planet with us!