Ever wondered how your body transforms sugar into energy?
Glycolysis is the first step in breaking down glucose.
It happens in your cells, and it's not just about energy—it's the start of a cellular adventure.
During glycolysis, glucose is split into two molecules of pyruvate.
But why is this important?
Because it sets the stage for what comes next!
This process produces ATP, your energy currency, and NADH, a key player in cellular respiration.
But there's a catch!
Not all pathways are perfectly efficient.
Understanding glycolysis isn't just for scientists.
It's the foundation of how our bodies fuel everything from a sprint to a simple thought.
So the next time you eat, remember this incredible process!
Curious about more science behind your body?
Hit like and follow for more!