Here's what science actually says about meninges basics.
Meninges are the protective layers enveloping your brain and spinal cord.
But did you know there are three distinct layers?
The outermost layer, the dura mater, is tough and durable.
The middle layer, the arachnoid, is web-like, while the innermost, the pia mater, is delicate and follows every contour.
These layers not only protect but also create a space filled with cerebrospinal fluid, which cushions the brain.
It’s vital for health.
Understanding meninges can reveal insights into conditions like meningitis.
Research is ongoing, with new findings every year!
Curious about more brain mysteries?
Hit like and follow for more science insights!