What if aging could run backwards?
Meet Turritopsis dohrnii — a jellyfish smaller than your fingernail, found in oceans around the world.
When it's injured, starving, or growing old, it doesn't simply fade away.
It sinks, collapses into a soft cyst… and then rebuilds itself as a polyp — the juvenile stage of its life.
Peer-reviewed research shows this life-cycle reversal is powered by rare cellular reprogramming called transdifferentiation.
Specialized cells change their identity — adult tissue becomes young tissue again.
Lab studies show it can reverse repeatedly under stress.
That is why it's called the immortal jellyfish.
But be careful with the myth: predators and disease can still kill individuals.
Immortal here means the life cycle can reset — not that nothing can harm it.
In one of the ocean's smallest bodies… evolution found a reset button.