Science tells a clearer story about clinical equipoise than social media ever could.
In simple terms, clinical equipoise is the ethical balance in clinical trials.
Researchers must genuinely not know which treatment is better.
But what happens when social media distorts this concept?
Misinformation can influence public perception and trust.
Studies show that maintaining equipoise is crucial for ethical research and patient safety.
Without it, trials can become biased.
Understanding clinical equipoise empowers you to question and engage with medical research more critically.
Curious about more science insights?
Hit that like button and subscribe for more!