Ever wondered how human activities affect whale communication?
Sonar whales rely on sound for navigation and hunting.
But what happens when our noise disrupts this delicate balance?
Studies show increased shipping traffic and naval exercises can interfere with their echolocation.
Research indicates that whales exposed to loud sounds can become disoriented, affecting their feeding and breeding.
This disruption not only harms individual whales but can impact entire populations, leaving lasting consequences.
Understanding these effects is crucial.
Knowing the facts helps us protect these magnificent creatures.
Curious to learn more about marine life?
Like and follow for more insights!