Science has a clearer story about nonhomologous end joining than social media does.
Nonhomologous end joining is a crucial DNA repair process that fixes breaks without needing a template.
Imagine your DNA is like a book.
Sometimes, pages tear.
Nonhomologous end joining just glues them back, but not always perfectly.
This method is fast but can lead to mutations.
It's like rushing to fix that page without reading what was lost.
Understanding this process helps scientists grasp cancer development and genetic disorders, revealing how our cells adapt under pressure.
Curious about how your body repairs itself?
Hit subscribe for more science insights!