Here's what science actually says about antiviral vs antibiotic.
Many confuse them, but they serve different purposes.
Antivirals target viruses, while antibiotics fight bacteria.
Simple, right?
Not so fast.
Imagine battling the flu with antibiotics!
It won’t work.
But why?
Because they’re designed for entirely different enemies.
Research indicates that using antibiotics against viruses can lead to resistance, making bacterial infections harder to treat.
So next time you’re sick, remember: choose the right treatment.
Ask your doctor for the best advice.
Curious for more science tips?
Like and follow for more insights!